原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译      Alex  秋乙一  Margaery  吃冰棒
翻译      ABCpril  dzysteven  capitaljack  一点都不酷喵
校对      free维塔  某羽
时间轴      大葱  Avis  岁半
后期      你是不是饿得慌
总监      free维塔
声明     人人视频非人人影视官方APP  与字幕组无关
傲骨之战
第一季 第七集
淘宝搜索店铺：我爱美剧创意周边
最新海外影视剧下载
微信扫描
上方二维码
关注TV哔
一起哔哔哔
雷迪克&博斯曼从一个当事人那里
Reddick/Boseman took an $800,000 bribe
受贿80万
from a client.
可能会惹上麻烦
It might be in trouble.
我不想让你惹祸上身
I don't want you to get in trouble.
知道了
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
怎么了
What's wrong?
科林·莫雷洛刚在我办公室
Colin Morrello was just in my office
警告我要和律所的财务保持距离
warning me to stay away from the firm's finances
因为...  我们收受了80万的贿赂
because... we took an $800,000 bribe.
这是我告诉我爸的说法
That's what I told my dad.
我知道
I know.
我知道你第一反应是想给他打电话
Look, I know your first instinct would be to call him,
但是为了律所...
but for the firm...
我们得告诉所有合伙人
We need to tell the partners.
我是迈克·克里斯特瓦
I'm Mike Kresteva,
司法部专案组的负责人  并且...
head of the DOJ task force, and...
我是斯宾塞·肖  助理联邦检察官
I'm Spencer Zschau, Assistant United States Attorney.
这家律所要对几起主要犯罪事件负责
This firm is responsible for several major crimes,
但首先我们把目光聚焦到其中两件...
but we're gonna start by focusing on just two of them...
受贿和逃税
bribery and tax evasion.
这家律所其中一个冠名合伙人
One of the name partners in the firm,
阿德里安·博斯曼  收受贿赂80万
Adrian Boseman, accepted an $800,000 bribe
帮助当事人逃税
to help a client evade taxes.
请记住  大陪审团承担的
Now, remember the burden of proof
举证责任很轻
on a grand jury is low.
你们的工作是起诉  不是定罪
Your job is merely to indict, not to convict.
所以请牢记于心
So please keep in mind
你们不需要排除一切合理怀疑去相信有罪
you don't need to believe beyond a reasonable doubt.
你们只要相信
You only need to believe
被告人有可能犯过罪行
that the accused could have committed a crime.
塔肖尼女士  这是联邦法官
Miss Tascioni, this is an order
强制要求你对我们的调查
from a federal magistrate compelling you
进行协助的指令
to assist in our investigation.
迈克  你好
Mike. Hi.
快进来
Well, come on in.
抱歉  我这儿没有足够的...  椅子
Oh, sorry, I don't have enough... chairs.
你是来逮捕我的吗
Are you here to arrest me?
不  我们要没收这个东西
No. We're here to confiscate that.
艾达  消除记录  清除所有文件
Ada, erase history. Purge all files.
明白  启动中
Understood. Activating.
恭喜  你刚刚篡改了证据
Congratulations, you just tampered with evidence.
「人类清除计划」是发行于2013年的
The Purge is a horror/sci-fi thriller
一部恐怖科幻惊悚片
premiering in 2013,
主演有伊桑·霍克和琳娜·海蒂...
starring Ethan Hawke and Lena Headey...
艾达  不要  取消
Ada, no! Cancel!
作为一名独立观察员  这种谈话
As the independent observer, this conversation
被定性为"不受保密"
is determined to be "Not privileged."
你在暗爽吧
You're enjoying this.
不  你我共事  我希望你能成功
No, I'm working with you. I want you to succeed.
你和克里斯特瓦说过什么
What were you asking about Kresteva?
好
Okay...
怎么了
What?
-好  -你听
- Yeah. - Listen.
但是没错  这个问题容易处理
But yes, this problem should be an easy fix.
倒填单据日期
Just back-date receipts.
重点是让克里斯特瓦相信有特拉维斯这个人
The important thing is that Kresteva believes Travis exists.
告诉我怎么回事
Just tell me what this is about.
坐好
Sit down.
发生了什么
What's going on?
你想要的我都做了
I gave you everything you needed.
你在和他们合作吗
Are you working with them?
我和他们合作  他们是谁
Am I working with them? Who's them?
雷迪克&博斯曼辩护团
The Reddick/Boseman defense team.
你在帮你女儿给我们传达假消息吗
Are you helping your daughter feed us false information?
没有  你在说什么
No. What are you talking about?
特拉维斯·利奥波德  根本没有受贿之事
Travis Leopold. There was no bribe.
根本没这个人
He doesn't exist.
塔肖尼女士在她的艾达设备上都说了
Ms. Tascioni admitted it on her Ada device.
现在有两种可能
Here are the two options.
要不是你在和他们合作
Either you're working with them,
要不就是你女儿知道你戴了窃听器
or your daughter knew you were wearing a wire
从而误导你
and misled you.
我得见见她
I have to see her.
不行  你们牢里见吧
No. She can see you in prison.
我们准备撤销你的保释
We're having your bail revoked.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
让我搞清楚到底怎么回事
Let me find out what happened.
-我不相信你  -求你了
- I can't trust you. - Please.
我得和她谈谈
I just need to talk to her.
你会录下谈话吗
You'll record it?
-家里来客人了吗  -没错
- Do we have company? - Oh, yes.
你爸来了
Your dad's here.
他在洗手间  给你
He's in the bathroom. Here.
-这是什么  -兰姆可乐
- What's this? - Rum and coke.
他来多久了
How long has he been here?
15分钟
15 minutes.
你们都聊些什么...
What have you guys been speaking ab...
该死
Shit.
怎么了  有什么事
What? What's wrong?
-你能帮我拖住他吗  -好
- Will you keep him occupied? - Okay.
亨利...  你真的不来一杯吗
Henry... are you sure you don't want a drink?
不  我觉得这对我保释没什么好处
No, I don't think it's a good idea with my bail.
玛娅  你好吗
Maia. How are you?
爸  挺好的
Dad. Good.
等我一下
Uh, will you give me a sec?
你家真漂亮  艾米
Your apartment looks beautiful, Amy.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们可能过一两个月就得搬家了
We may have to move in a month or two.
为什么啊
Oh, why's that?
钱的问题  爸
Money, Dad.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
你们俩先聊
Why don't I let you two talk.
很高兴见到你  艾米
Good to see you, Amy.
我也是  亨利
You, too, Henry.
我们得谈谈
We should talk.
我们谈过了
We did.
对
Yes.
但再谈一次
But once more.
等我们想开诚布公时告诉我一声  爸
Tell me when we're being honest, Dad,
我会愿意说实话的
and I'll be sure to switch over.
你不相信我
You didn't trust me.
你上次向我说了谎
You told me a lie last time.
你们公司根本没有受贿
There was no bribery at your firm.
天呐  天呐
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
这就是场闹剧  爸
This is a farce, Dad.
你戴了窃听器
You were wearing a wire.
我对你说谎是事出有因的
If I told you a lie, there was a reason.
让我们来场父女间的谈话  好吗
Talk to me like I'm your daughter, okay?
我就在这里
I am right here.
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
怎么不是了
Why isn't it?
好了
Okay.
我们开诚布公吧
Here we are.
我这样做不是为了自保
I'm not doing this to save my skin.
他们冲着你来了
They're coming after you.
为什么
For what?
基金
The foundation.
你在转移基金的文件上签了字
Your signature on the transferred funds.
那是伪造的
They were forged.
亲爱的  我觉得他们不会这样认为
Honey, I don't think they'll believe that.
你是说  你录下我们的谈话
You're saying you were recording our conversations
用它来对付我的律所
and using them against my law firm
是明显在为我好吗
out of some clear concern for me?
没错
Yes.
联调局威胁说要起诉你
The Feds are threatening to prosecute you.
-他们在撒谎  -他们没有
- They're lying. - No, they're not.
我的天  那就别他妈利用我
Oh, my God, then don't fucking use me
来消除你的愧疚感  爸爸
to clear your conscience, Dad.
你想为自己做笔交易  那就去
You want to make a deal for yourself, do it.
别说是为了我
Don't do it for me.
他们在你律师的录音里找到了那段谎言
They discovered the lie on your lawyer's recording.
他们知道贿赂的事是杜撰的了
They found out the bribery was made up.
我为什么要相信你  爸爸
Why do I trust you, Dad?
因为
Because in, um,
十分钟后
in ten minutes,
你的合伙人们就会收到传票
your partners will be subpoenaed.
明天他们就会被拉到大陪审团前面
Tomorrow they'll be dragged in front of the grand jury.
克里斯特瓦不在乎能否定罪
Kresteva doesn't care about a conviction.
他只想要一张起诉书
All he wants is an indictment
就能毁了你们律所
to destroy your firm.
有五种法式酱料必不可缺
There are five essential French sauces.
如果想学做法国菜
If you are to learn French cuisine,
这些酱料就是基础
these are foundational.
这个奶酱做得很不错  阿德里安
Now, that is a beautiful velouté, Adrian.
谢谢
Ah, merci.
大家都过来看看阿德里安的成果
Everyone, come and look at Adrian's work here.
你们都要向他学习
This is what you want to imitate.
-博斯曼先生  -是我
- Mr. Boseman. - Oui.
你被传唤了
You've been served.
我很高兴你打给了我
I'm glad you called me.
我昨天还在想大学时候的事
I was thinking about college just yesterday.
我们要怎么征服世界
How we were gonna rule the world...
你基本上已经做到了  不是吗
Which you basically did, didn't you?
有什么特色菜吗
Are there any specials?
不知道  我没看宣传牌
I don't know. I didn't see the board.
我不是你服务生
I'm not your waiter.
芭芭拉·科斯达  你被传唤了
Barbara Kolstad, you've been served.
八位合伙人  四名律师被传唤
Eight partners subpoenaed, four associates.
他没查到什么
He's got nothing on us.
他没法立案
He has no case.
他不需要立案  芭芭拉
He doesn't need one, Barbara.
他还是能把我们拖到大陪审团面前
He'll still drag us in front of the grand jury,
大喊几声「反诈骗腐败组织集团犯罪法」
scream "RICO."
不管怎样他都能拿到起诉书
He gets his indictment no matter what.
-我同意  -你同意吗
- I agree. - You do?
是的
Yes.
大陪审团总会选择起诉
Grand juries always indict.
除非是警方施暴案
Unless it's a police brutality case.
除此之外还有个问题是
And then there's the additional problem
克里斯特瓦不相信那个受贿故事了
that Kresteva no longer believes our bribery story.
所以我们要怎么做
So what do we do?
他要的不是定罪
Well, he doesn't want a conviction.
我喜欢这耳环  尤其喜欢这形状
I like those earrings. Especially the shape.
谢谢
Thanks?
希望我也能戴这种耳环
I wish I could wear earrings like that,
-但会显得我无精打采  -埃尔斯贝特
- but they make my face droopy. - Elsbeth.
没错  抱歉  你太棒了
Right. Sorry. You're amazing.
他想让你们破产
Um, he wants to bankrupt you.
没错  我接到了佩斯里集团的电话
Right. I got a call from the Paisley Group.
昨天有联邦探员过去
There was a federal agent over there yesterday
问了一些关于我们的问题
asking questions about us.
他想吓跑我们的客户
He's trying to scare off our clients.
怎么了
What?
-怎么  -不  我说你怎么了
- What? - No, you. What?
-你本想说些什么的  -不  我只是
- You were about to say something. - No, I just...
我不知道这有没有用
I'm not sure if this helps,
但克里斯特瓦的上司
but Kresteva's boss,
助理总检察长
the assistant attorney general,
在担心这调查显得有些
was concerned that the investigation was seeming...
种族歧视
racist.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我只是知道而已
I... I just know.
这样可行
That's a possibility.
什么可行
What's a possibility?
我不太想直接说出来
Uh, well, I don't want to say it.
我们是非裔美国人的律所
We're an African-American firm
被一个大多为白人的部门起诉
being persecuted by a majority white department?
你想让我们把回答引到种族问题上来吗
You want us to turn our answers toward race?
没错
Yes.
阻止被起诉的唯一办法
The only way to prevent an indictment
是停掉大陪审团
is to close down the grand jury.
而停掉大陪审团的唯一办法
And the only way to close down the grand jury
是说服助理总检察长威尔伯·丁肯
is to convince Wilbur Dincon, the assistant attorney general,
这事对他没好处
it's not in his interest.
而要说服他这事对他没好处的唯一办法
And the only way to convince him it's not in his interest
就是把回答引导到种族的问题上来
is to turn our answers toward race.
没错  我们只有一个观众  威尔伯·丁肯
Yep. We have an audience of one: Wilbur Dincon.
芭芭拉  你觉得呢
Barbara, what do you think?
打种族的牌吗
About using race?
那这就是种族的问题了
Well, it is about race.
阿德里安·博斯曼
Adrian Boseman.
我是雷迪克&博斯曼&科斯达律所的律师
I'm an attorney with the firm of Reddick, Boseman & Kolstad,
中西部最大的非裔美国人律所
the largest African-American firm in the Midwest.
被「美国律师」誉为国内前十的
Named by American Lawyer as one of the top ten
黑人律所
black firms in the country.
你说完了吗
You finished?
说完了
Yeah.
博斯曼先生  你在芝加哥当了多久的律师
Mr. Boseman, how long have you practiced law in Chicago?
35年
35 years.
我由哈罗德·华盛顿市长宣誓入职
I was sworn in by Mayor Harold Washington,
他是市里首位也是唯一一位黑人市长
the city's first and, so far, only black mayor.
其实我口袋里都还揣着张他的照片
I actually keep a photograph of him in my pocket just to
时刻提醒着我
remind me of the struggles of
那些在之前奋斗过
black people who've come before and...
为我铺平道路的黑人们
paved the way for me.
好了  谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
你会同意说  起诉芝加哥警局
Would you agree that suing the Chicago Police Department
是你们律所的主要收益流吗
has been a major income stream for your firm?
我同意我们的律所
I agree that our firm,
是一家由非裔美国人多数参股的律所
as a majority-owned African-American firm...
女士  我并没有问贵所的种族成分
Ma'am, I didn't ask about your racial makeup.
是的  但是你让我用自己的话来表达的
Yes, but you did ask me to answer in my own words,
这就是我的话啊
and these are my own words.
请继续
Please, continue.
谢谢
Thank you.
就像我说的
As I said, there's no mistaking that,
作为一家由非裔美国人拥有的律所
as an African-American owned firm...
威尔伯·丁肯
助理总检察长
"某些受害者会觉得到我们律所来
"...certain victims feel more comfortable coming to us
比去由白人控股的律所更舒服
than to a majority Caucasian firm."
提问  "再说一遍  这跟种族无关  女士"
Question, "Again, this is not about race, ma'am."
回答  "是你问上下文剧语境的  先生
Answer, "You asked for context, sir,
而语境里就包含我们律所的种族成分"
and the context involves the racial makeup of our firm."
什么情况
What the hell is going on?
你本应该跟种族不沾边的
You were supposed to stay away from race.
我们没沾  不是我们提出来的  是他们
We are. We're not the ones taking it there, they are.
我不管谁提的
I don't care who is.
这事看上去像迫害了
It's looking like a persecution.
是策略
It's a tactic.
那就绕过它
Well, then, go around it.
你必须澄清此案跟种族无关
You need to make it clear that this is not about race.
我想做一条鲨鱼
...vita voglio essere uno squalo.
来生  我愿做一条鲨鱼
Nella miah prosseema vita voglio essere uno squalo.
叨咕什么呢
What's that?
意大利语
Italian.
为什么
Why?
我一直都想学意大利语
I always wanted to learn Italian.
你真是个奇怪的孩子
You are an odd child.
你知道我在说什么吗
You know what I'm saying?
"来生  我愿做一条鲨鱼"
"In my next life, I want to come back as a shark."
很好  说得通
Great. Makes sense to me.
梅丽莎·戈德  对吧
Marissa Gold, right?
不  来生  我愿做一条鲨鱼
No. Nella mia prossima vita voglio essere uno squalo.
那太糟糕了  此生  你被传唤了
所以  他在转移话题
So, he's pivoting?
正确  不能再说黑人律师了
Exactly. No more black lawyers.
现在  他冲着你们三个来
Now, he's going after you three.
为什么
For what?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们很快就会知道了
We'll find out soon enough.
我们定在明天见大陪审团
We're scheduled for the grand jury tomorrow.
好消息是
And the good news,
我们有一个观众
we have an audience.
是的  威尔伯·丁肯正在关注此案
Yep. Wilbur Dincon is paying attention.
我们如何利用这一点呢
So, how do we exploit that?
咱们想想吧
Well, let's think.
咱们......
Let's...
我们不想让哪个大陪审团的人将事情联系起来
So, we don't want a grand jury to connect the dots.
我们想要的是一个有意义的案子
What we want is a case that makes sense...
如果没有事实支撑的话  我们没法定罪
we won't get a conviction unless the facts hold up.
我们稍后再考虑这个
Let's worry about this later.
大陪审团很感情用事
Grand juries work off of emotion.
首先  我们需要起诉书
First, we need an indictment.
我们需要有事实支撑的起诉书
Well, we need an indictment based on facts.
你好
Uh, hello?
你想做什么
Do you need something?
你知道我每发一封传票能挣多少钱吗
Do you know how much I make for every subpoena I deliver?
不知道
No idea,
但是我确定你可以跟治安官办公室里聊聊这事
but I'm sure you can talk to the sheriff's office about this.
47美元
$47.
很好  真棒
Great. Good to know.
过去的48小时过得真的特别棒
And this has been a really good 48 hours.
你被传唤了
You've been served.
迈克  你好吗
Mike, how are you?
你回来了
You're back.
你好  塔肖尼女士
Hello, Miss Tascioni.
你贪多嚼不烂了
You have bitten off way more than you can chew.
是吗  我挺能嚼的呢
Really? I can chew a lot.
你在民事法庭对我提起诉讼
You're suing me in civil court?
是的  因为侵权干涉合约关系
Yes, for tortious interference with contractual relations.
我觉得挺聪明的
I thought that was clever.
你不会真这么觉得吧
You don't believe it?
我就像你相信大陪审团一样相信这个
I believe it the same way you do your grand jury.
在你们被起诉的同时
No court will allow you to sue me
没有法庭会允许你起诉我
at the same time that you're being prosecuted.
也许你是说得对  迈克
Maybe you're right, Mike.
你吃不吃无无花果软糖
Hmm. Do you want a fig bar?
不吃
No.
也许你说得对
Maybe you're right that
没有哪个法庭会让我的诉讼继续下去
no court will allow my suit to go forward,
但是你打电话告诉我就行了
but you could've told me that on the phone.
相反  你来我这了
Instead, you came over here.
当然  随时欢迎
And you're welcome anytime.
我们法庭见
I'll see you in court.
两个庭
Both courts.
咱们走着瞧  看哪个先结束
We'll see which one finishes first.
放那堆文件的最上面的话
Putting something on top of the pile
可是让我把它挪到最下面的最好办法了
is a great way to get me to move it to the bottom.
我认为博斯曼先生不会喜欢这个做法
I don't think Mr. Boseman would like that.
这是什么
What is this?
不知道
No idea.
这是跟林德尔庞氏骗局案相关的东西
It's something regarding the Rindell Ponzi scheme.
这些是「财富」500强名单
Well, these are Fortune 500 names.
并不全
Not all of them,
只是一部分
but some.
但是你看看这些数字
But look at these numbers here.
九位数  代表什么
Nine digit numbers. What are they?
不知道  社保账号
No idea. Social Security numbers?
不是  我查过了
No, I checked.
好吧
Okay.
勾起了我的好奇心
My curiosity is whetted.
我也是  我喜欢神秘的东西
Me, too. I like mysteries.
你能查出来
Could you find out
这份名单能如何打击到这家律所吗
how this list might come back to hurt this firm?
确定它不利于我们吗
Are we sure it will?
确定
Oh, yes.
克里斯特瓦先生费尽心机想得到它
Mr. Kresteva worked too hard to get it.
好的  我会查一查的
Okay. I'll take a look.
谢谢
Thank you.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding?
没有  我要把你加进来  孩子
No. I'm putting you in, kid.
长官  别...
Sir, please. It's not...
我讨厌他
I hate him.
我明白了
Oh, I see.
你是不是错误地认为
Are you under the mistaken impression
你只会为你喜欢的人辩护
that you only defend people you like?
不是  我错误地认为
No, I'm under the mistaken impression
我不为任何人辩护  我是一名检察官
I don't defend anyone. I'm a prosecutor.
是啊  好吧
Yeah, well,
什么时候你能让这个扯淡的侵权干涉案子撤案
when you get this tortious interference nonsense dismissed,
你就能继续回来做检察官
you can go back to prosecuting.
长官  我得告诉你此事与我有利益冲突
Sir. I have to... apprise you of a conflict of interest.
什么利益冲突
And what's that?
我在和原告律所的一名律师约会
I'm dating one of the lawyers at the plaintiff's firm.
明白了
I see.
这不是一件好事
That's not good.
是的  我不确定自己能否保持客观
Yeah, I'm, uh, not sure that I could be... objective.
我同意
I agree.
不要和她约会了
Stop dating her.
然后你就能保持客观了
Then you can be.
你上庭要迟到了
You're late for court.
凯尔·伽洛法官
老天  其他人呢
Jesus Christ, where is everybody?
现在已经上午十点了  是吗
It's 10 A.M. Am I right?
没错  法官阁下  原告方已经就绪
You are right, Your Honor. The plaintiffs are ready.
很好  别拍我马屁
Good for you. Stop kissing my ass.
-被告呢  -我来了  法官阁下
- Where's the defense? - I'm here, Your Honor.
你迟到了  你让我在这傻等
You're late. You had me waiting.
很抱歉  法官阁下
My apologies, Your Honor.
我刚被指派接手这个案子
I was just assigned this case.
关我屁事
I don't give a shit.
我们十点开始  你就得十点到
We start at 10:00, you're here at 10:00.
今天是什么案子  侵权干涉
What do we have today? Tortious interference.
是的  法官阁下  这间律所...
Yes, Your Honor. This law firm...
我们请求立即撤案
We ask for an immediate motion to dismiss.
住嘴
Stop it.
你先说  迟到先生
You first, Mr. Late.
被告动议撤案
Uh, the defense moves to dismiss.
克里斯特瓦先生正在进行一场大陪审团调查
Mr. Kresteva is in the middle of an active Grand Jury Investigation.
发起这些诉讼是想对此事
Initiating these proceedings
进行干扰  这是损人利己的做法
is a cynical attempt to interfere with that.
强烈反对
Vehemently disagree.
阿德里安
Adrian.
早上好  法官阁下
Good morning, Your Honor.
克里斯特瓦先生的大陪审团调查...
Mr. Kresteva's Grand Jury Investigation...
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
他是律师还是原告
Is he the lawyer or the plaintiff?
原告
The plaintiff.
那他不应该在法庭之上进行辩护
Well, then, he shouldn't be arguing in court.
他应该作为证人被传召
He should be called as a witness.
那我想传召阿德里安·博斯曼先生作为证人上庭
Oh. Then, I'd like to call Mr. Adrian Boseman as a witness.
不行  打断一下  不行  不...
No, excuse me, no. No. Uh... uh,
法官阁下  你还没有听我的撤案动议
Your Honor, you never heard on my motion to dismiss.
是  但你刚让他们让他作为证人出庭
Yeah, but you just told them to put him on the stand.
不  我说他不应该在法庭上进行辩护
No, I-I said he shouldn't be arguing in court.
辩护方在利用这个民事权利...
The defense is using this civil action...
"原告"  你应该指的是这个吧
"The plaintiff"? Is that the word you're looking for?
是的
Yes.
原告...
The plaintiff...
利用这个民事诉讼  妄图发现点什么
is using this civil action as a poor man's discovery.
他们没有机会进入我们的大陪审团房间
They don't have access to our Grand Jury room,
于是他们试图利用这个法庭去试探...
so they are using this court as a way to find out...
大陪审团的动态
uh, what's going on in the grand jury room.
这是你们的企图吗  律师
Is that what you were doing, counselor?
不是  法官阁下
No, Your Honor.
我要是有这么聪明就好了
I wish I were that smart.
这个主意不错
Good idea.
好吧  反对无效  传唤你的证人
Okay, overruled, call your witness.
埃尔斯贝特
Elsbeth.
让我做你的次席律师
Make me your second chair.
为什么
Why?
因为这是个好主意
Because it's a good idea.
博斯曼先生  为什么你要起诉他们侵权干涉
Mr. Boseman, why are you suing for tortious interference?
我们的客户在流失
We're losing clients.
上两个星期我们失去了三名客户
Three clients in the past two weeks.
为什么这个案子现在开审对你很重要
And why is it important that this case be heard now?
因为这个大陪审团就是我们客户流失的原因
Because this Grand Jury is the reason we're losing clients.
克里斯特瓦先生并不是想要定罪
Mr. Kresteva doesn't want a conviction.
他想要我们破产
He wants our bankruptcy.
反对  引导证人推测
Objection. Speculation.
这个反对只能对我的问题有效
Uh, that's a proper objection for a question,
但对回答无效
not for a response.
如果莫雷洛先生有反证证人
If Mr. Morrello has a rebuttal witness,
他应该让他出庭
he should present him.
我同意  反对无效
I would agree. Overruled.
博斯曼先生
Mr. Boseman,
有客户向你解释了他们离开的原因吗
did any of your clients explain why they were leaving?
有  佩斯利集团说
Yes. The Paisley Group said
联邦探员到他们的工作地点
federal agents came to their workplace
盘问我们的工作
questioning them about our work.
他们不想惹麻烦
They didn't want the hassle.
你认为这是克里斯特瓦先生的干涉行为
And you think this was an intentional move
导致的吗
on Mr. Kresteva's part?
-反对  -当然
- Objection. - Absolutely.
这次也是引导证人推测
This time calls for speculation.
瞧瞧  你能做出合理反对了
Look at you, making a proper objection.
反对有效
Sustained.
我没有问题了  法官阁下
Nothing further, Your Honor.
我问完了  莫雷洛先生
Your witness, Mr. Morrello.
谢谢  奎因女士
Thank you, Ms. Quinn.
你失去的这三位客户
These three clients you lost,
他们对你们的财务影响有多大
how important were they to your bottom line?
每位客户都非常重要
Every client is important.
这听起来并没有很重要
Hmm. That sounds like not very important.
反对  非常牵强  有争议
Objection. Lamely argumentative.
对  在我看来也是
Yeah, no, it sounded that way to me, too.
这三位客户的离开
How much money a year do you lose
使你一年损失了多少钱
from losing these three clients?
我想  130万美元
I guess... $1.3 million.
但我们不能再这样下去了  法官阁下
But that's why we need to stop this leakage now, Your Honor.
你们不是刚刚和查查网签约了吗
And didn't you just sign Chumhum,
一个社交媒体巨头
a massive social media empire
每年可以向你的律所贡献8600万美元
worth $86 million a year to you?
-是的  -那么  130万美元
- Yes, we did. - So... $1.3 million
对比8600万美元
versus $86 million.
二者并无关联
Those two things are not connected.
别在这哭穷
Whah-whah-whah-whah, don't cry poverty in here!
我们不是在哭穷
Oh, we're not crying poverty.
奎因女士很明显是想
Ms. Quinn clearly wants to avoid any oversight...
我们只是说司法部
We're just saying that the DOJ
故意想将...
is intentionally trying to take something...
每次搞点小偷小摸时
...by officials and every time they have their hands
都能逃过有关部门的监管
caught in the cookie jar...
不不不  你们两个  都回座位去
No, no, no. Both of you, back in your seats.
注意礼节
Decorum.
这是我一贯主张的
That's what I insist on.
抱歉  法官阁下
My apologies, Your Honor.
我能问个问题吗
May I ask a quick question?
可以  小声点儿
You may, quietly.
被告为什么不出庭呢
Why is the defendant not here?
我看到只有被告律师来了
I see that the defense sent its lawyer,
难道被告觉得这次庭审无足轻重
but does the defendant think so little of this court
才只派律师出庭吗
that he only sends his lawyer?
我相信原告律师知道原因
I believe the plaintiff's lawyer knows the reason.
被告正忙着大陪审团问询的事
The defendant is busy running a grand jury room.
这样啊  所以克里斯特瓦先生
I see. So, Mr. Kresteva
抽不出空给伽洛法官对吗
is too busy for Judge Gallo?
你有解释我在主持大陪审团问询吗
Did you explain that I'm conducting a grand jury?
说了  可主审是伽洛法官  他讨厌被人轻视
I did. It's Judge Gallo. He doesn't like being dissed.
天哪  好吧  什么时候开庭
Dear God. Okay, when?
今天下午
This afternoon.
目前的情形正合他们意  你看出来了吧
This is playing right into their hands. You know that.
当然
I sure do.
那么  戈德女士
So, Ms. Gold,
你和戴安·洛哈特是什么关系呢
what is your relationship with Diane Lockhart?
她是我的老板
She's my boss.
-我还将她视为我的导师  -是吗
- Also, I consider her my mentor. -Really?
她教你什么了
What does she mentor you in?
自从进入非裔律所工作
Well, since coming to work at an African-American firm,
我得说是让我开始意识了到白人特权
I'd say it's becoming aware of the nature of white privilege.
你曾与洛哈特女士在她之前的律所共事过
And you worked with Ms. Lockhart at her previous firm,
-是吗  -没错
- did you not? - I did,
但那里绝对和非裔美国人没关系
but that was definitely not an African-American firm.
完全跟特朗普的白宫似的
It was like the Trump White House there.
戈德女士  我们不是在问
Ms. Gold, we're not asking
这家律所的种族问题
about the racial makeup of the firm.
不好意思
Oh, sorry.
真敏感
Touchy.
你是否注意到
You were aware, were you not,
洛哈特女士在去阿德里安·博斯曼的律所前
that Ms. Lockhart had frequent meetings and phone calls
就和他有频繁会面及电话来往
with Adrian Boseman prior to going over to his firm?
有
Absolutely.
博斯曼先生的律所曾替一位
Mr. Boseman's firm was representing a young, African-American man
遭白人警官毒打的年轻美国黑人辩护
who had been pretty severely beaten by a white police officer...
再次申明  这与种族无关  女士
Again, this is not about race, ma'am.
我同意  不过是你们一直在问这方面问题
I agree, but you guys keep asking me about race.
那洛哈特女士是否向博斯曼先生透露过
Isn't it true that Ms. Lockhart slipped privileged information
这件案子的保密信息吗
to Mr. Boseman about this case?
你是指被白人警察毒打的黑人
You mean the case about this African-American kid
这个案子吗
being beaten up by the white cops?
不好意思  但是你先问的
I'm sorry, but you asked the question.
喂  戴安  我感觉进展很顺利
Hey, Diane. I think it went great.
好的
Uh, yeah.
好  我马上回去
Okay, I'm on my way back.
安德鲁·哈特
It's Andrew Hart.
他有什么把柄
What does he have on us?
为什么克里斯特瓦叫他来作证
Why is Kresteva calling him to testify?
他旁边有别人吗
Did you see him with anybody else?
-没  就他一个  -我们得弄清楚
- No, he was alone. - We need to find out
他对大陪审团都说了我们律所什么
what he said to the grand jury about our firm.
怎么弄清楚
How do we do that?
关于原告的律所  你是怎么对大陪审团说的
What did you say to the grand jury about the plaintiff's firm?
反对  大陪审团问询内容属于机密
Objection. Grand jury proceedings are under seal
不能公之于众  无论塔肖尼女士
and cannot be made public, no matter how clever
觉得自己有多聪明都不行
Ms. Tascioni thinks she is.
反对有效
Sustained.
太过奖了
That's sweet,
夸我聪明
complimenting me for being clever.
谢谢
Thank you.
很高兴见到你  克里斯特瓦先生
Nice to see you, Mr. Kresteva.
迪尔德拉好吗
Oh, how's Diedre?
她很好
Oh, she's fine.
嘿  这是法庭
Uh, hello? Civil court.
-纳税人的钱可一直烧着呢  -抱歉
- Taxpayers' money being spent. - Yes, sorry.
我是否可以说
Is it fair to say that
为了获得竞争优势
in an effort to gain some competitive advantage,
你曾试图让阿德里安·博斯曼被取消律师资格呢
you sought to have Adrian Boseman disbarred?
是否可以  不可以
Is it fair? No, it's not fair.
知道了
I see.
那是否可以说你试图劝说
Well, is it fair to say that you tried calling
他是否想让我被吊销律师执照
他有没有联系我们的客户
他和谁联系过
多少客户
雷迪克&博斯曼律所的客户离开他们呢
Reddick & Boseman clients to steal them away?
不  也不能这么说
No, that's not fair, either.
一点也没有吗
Not even a little bit?
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
这是钓鱼盘问
This is a fishing expedition.
是吗
Yes?
就是...
It's...
我说的这样
...what I said.
塔肖尼女士  你到底想干吗
Ms. Tascioni, where is this going?
我只有几个问题要问了
I just have a few more questions.
你是否与雷迪克&博斯曼律所的客户见面
Did you ever meet with Reddick & Boseman clients
好挖走他们呢  可以这么说吗
in order to steal them away? Is that fair?
我所做的一切都在法律范围之内
I have not done anything illegal.
我没问这个
That's not my question.
你是否与雷迪克&博斯曼律所的客户见面
Did you ever meet with Reddick & Boseman clients
好挖走他们呢
with the direct intent of stealing them?
哪个客户
我只是做了任何生意人都会做的事
I did what any business would do.
哪位客户呢  哈特先生
Which client, Mr. Hart?
反对  与本案无关
Objection. Relevance?
他们只不过想证明证人对大陪审团
They're just trying to establish that the witness is feeding
透露了不利信息
negative info to the grand jury,
这样他就能挖走他们的客户了
so he can steal their clients.
没错  法官阁下
Exactly, Your Honor.
女士  我知道你习惯大声说话了
Ma'am, you're an acquired taste,
但我还没习惯  所以
and I don't think I've acquired it yet, so... shh.
请回答问题
Please answer the question.
我同一位叫施皮格尔的先生吃了午餐
I met for lunch with a Mr. Spiegel,
他经营连锁百货商店
who owns a string of department stores.
去找施皮格尔  哈特想挖走他
Get to Spiegel. Hart's trying to poach him.
你心情很不好吗
Are you in a pissy mood?
没有
No.
那晚上来我家吧
Then come by tonight.
有人让我和你分手
I've been told to break up with you.
有人
You've been told?
真的吗
Really?
那你最好照做咯
Then you'd better do it.
不然你会被炒的
You're going to get fired.
反正我也讨厌这工作
Mm, I hate my job, anyway.
施皮格尔先生  最近好吗
Mr. Spiegel, how are you?
不错
Good.
我想既然是你打电话给我的
I hope since you called me
那我应该不会要付钱吧
I'm not getting billed for this.
计时器停了
Meter's off.
我们这周安排和一些客户聊了聊
We're sitting down with some of our clients this week.
只是想确定没有忽视任何事
We just want to make sure we're not missing anything,
客户的需求都得到了满足
their needs are being met...
以及没人弃船而去吗
And no one's jumping ship?
当下有人针对我们律所的进行抹黑  安东尼
There's a smear campaign against our firm, Anthony.
我想澄清一下谣言
I want to set the record straight.
你想知道谁在我耳边打小报告
You want to know who's been whispering in my ear.
如果让我猜一下
If I were to guess,
我觉得近期应该是安迪·哈特
I'd say lately it's coming from Andy Hart.
你猜得没错
You'd be right.
介意告诉我他说了什么吗
Mind telling me what he said?
他警告我说
He warned me
雷迪克&博斯曼正被卷入一场大风暴之中
that Reddick/Boseman was in the path of a major storm.
说我要是明智的话
And that I would be wise
应该现在开始物色其他律所了
to seek other representation.
他有没有提到什么关于大陪审团
Did he say anything about a grand jury
已经组成的事情
having been impaneled?
反对
Objection.
法官阁下  我并没有问大陪审团
Your Honor, I'm not asking about the content
问询的具体内容
of the grand jury proceeding.
我只是想知道  哈特先生有没有用
All I want to know is, did Mr. Hart use the fact
他要在大陪审团面前作证这一事实
that he testified before the grand jury
来窃取雷迪克&博斯曼的客户
to steal Reddick/Boseman clients?
对窃取这一措辞提出反对
Objection as to stealing.
能让我完整说完一句话而不进行反对吗
Can I get out one statement without an objection?
当然可以  只要你不用"窃取"这样
Sure, just don't use loaded words
有暗示意味的字眼
like "stealing."
好吧  这两个反对
Okay, which one of your objections
你希望我先裁决哪一个  律师
would you like me to rule on first, counselor?
第一  第二个吧
The fir... uh, the second.
反对无效
Overruled.
你现在想听听我对第一个反对的裁决吗
Would you like to hear about the first one now?
同样反对无效
Overruled.
先生  哈特先生有提到他的证词吗
Sir, did Mr. Hart mention his testimony?
没有
No.
谢谢
Thank you.
因为他当时还没出席作证
Because he hadn't testified yet.
你是什么时候和哈特先生会面的
Uh, when was it that you met with Mr. Hart?
两周前
Two weeks ago.
他当时有提到大陪审团将就位进行问询吗
And did he mention that a grand jury would be impaneled?
据我回忆
As I recall,
那是他整场游说的核心要点
it was the centerpiece of his presentation.
我想提请法庭注意
I would direct the court's attention
汤姆·C·戈登来电
这一事件发生在除了克里斯特瓦先生
to the fact that this would've been
办公室里的员工以外任何人都无法得知
before anyone outside of Mr. Kresteva's office
将会有一次大陪审团问询之前
would have known about a grand jury.
奎因女士到底是在询问一位证人还是在作证
Is Ms. Quinn questioning a witness or testifying?
我只是想指出显而易见的事实
I'm just pointing out the obvious.
我最喜爱的诉讼投资人近来如何呀
How are my favorite litigation financiers?
很不好  博斯曼先生
Not good, Mr. Boseman.
我们刚刚被传唤要在大陪审团前作证
We just got subpoenaed to testify before the grand jury.
该死的
Oh, shit.
诉讼投资人
Litigation financiers.
真是个有意思的头衔
What an interesting title.
你俩在哪上的法学院
Where'd you guys go to law school?
我们没读过法律
We didn't.
那你们能解释一下你们是如何直接参与到
Then can you explain how you've been directly involved
超过75起民事案件中的吗
in over 75 civil cases?
我们为律所提供融资服务
We provide financing to law firms
以便让他们在短时间内手头有大笔官司时
that allows them to cover operating costs
获取周转资金来支付必要的运营成本
while undertaking time-intensive legal battles.
比如像雷迪克&博斯曼这间律所
Law firms like Reddick/Boseman.
你们为多少个案子提供了资金支持
How many of their cases have you bankrolled?
-21个  -不
- Twenty-one. - No.
是23个
23.
你是怎么算的
Wha... how do you figure?
还有那次上诉和圣诞节的庭外和解
The appeal and the Christmas settlement.
不  是21个
No, that's 21.
不对  21加2是23
No, 21 plus two is 23.
就是21个
It's 21 period.
好了  先别管是21还是23了
Okay, let's leave it at 21 or 23.
雷迪克&博斯曼律所为你们提供什么
What does Reddick/Boseman give you
作为融资的回报呢
in return for this financing?
我们约定将庭外和解金额的一部分作为报酬
An agreed upon percentage of the settlement amount.
我假定雷迪克&博斯曼律所支付给你们的是
Well, I assume Reddick/Boseman
他们从庭外和解总金额中所获佣金的一部分
pays you your percentage out of theirs.
你是真的这么假定还是你只是想
Do you really assume that or are you just trying
通过说你假定来表达一个观点
to make a point by saying you assume it?
报酬百分比是按什么计算的  华少夫斯基先生
Where does the percentage come from, Mr. Warshofsky?
是23  不是21
It's 23, not 21.
好了  杰瑞  就
Okay, Jerry, j-just...
按照如果没有我们投资  委托人根本收不到的
From the client's percentage of money he never would've seen
那笔和解金中的一定百分比计算
if it weren't for the money we invested.
谢谢
Thank you.
在2月20日  就在达成庭外和解之前
On February 20, just before the settlement,
你们二位决定通过继续往此案中注资的方式
you gentlemen decided to increase your stake in the case
提高你们投资的分成比例  为什么会这么做
by investing more money. Why was that?
博斯曼先生非常自信他们将
Mr. Boseman was confident they'd
争取到500万美元的赔偿金
come in north of five million.
他有告诉你们他这么有信心的依据是什么吗
Did he tell you the basis for this confidence?
他有个内部消息来源
He had a-a source on the other side
告诉他对方愿意以此金额进行庭外和解
who told him they were ready to settle.
当时的这个对方内部消息来源是戴安·洛哈特
The other side at the time being Diane Lockhart.
博斯曼先生有没有告诉你们
Did Mr. Boseman tell you
对方出于什么原因这么急于达成和解呢
what the other side was nervous about?
他们发现了一项如果上庭
They-they discovered a piece of evidence
会对他们不利的证据
that would hurt them if they went to trial.
他跟我们说我们不允许跟任何人说
He told us that we're not allowed to-to tell anyone
我们在问询中被问了些什么问题
what they asked us in there.
没错  但你可以告诉我们你们说了些什么
Well, that's true, but you can tell us what you said.
这就是言论自由了
That's free speech.
-我  -我不想搅这趟浑水
- I... - I don't like getting involved in this.
-我们走吧  -等等  留步
- Let's go. - Wait, wait. One second.
我们一起赚了很多钱
Now, we have made a lot of money together.
-对吗  -没错
- Right? - Right.
那么你们是不是聊到了我们经手的一个案子
So, did you talk about one of our cases?
是某个警察暴力执法的案子吗
Was it one of the police brutality cases?
是我们正在代理的案子吗
Is it the one we're running now?
不是
No.
我觉得我们不应该继续回答问题了
I don't think we should answer any more.
我知道  但是
I-I know, but...
就再问一个问题
Just one more question.
是我和戴安共同代理的某案子吗
Is it a case that Diane and I worked on together?
是的  但不是共同代理的
Yeah, but not together.
妈的
Fuck.
但请别说脏话  好吗
But hey, please, don't swear, okay?
-好的  我明白  -我们
- Ah! Okay. I-I-I got it. - We...
会吓到杰
It bugs out Jer.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
谢谢  谢谢你们能来
And thank you. Thank you for coming.
-祝你们好运  -谢谢
- Yeah. Yeah, good luck. - Thank you.
让我来
Let me get that.
谢谢
Appreciate it.
不客气
Yeah, yeah.
这跟托比·肯德尔先生的案子有关
It's about the Toby Kendall case.
他们是想指控我
They're coming after me
告诉你摄像头证据的那件事
for telling you about the camera evidence.
你没告诉过我任何有关摄像头证据的事
You didn't tell me about any camera evidence.
你让我雇佣了一个律师
You told me to hire an associate
然后  是她发现了证据
who, in turn, discovered evidence.
不  我没有  我透露了更多的信息给你
No, I didn't. I told you more.
而那足以吊销我的律师执照了
That's disbarrable.
戴安
Diane.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们都知道  有时我们会游走在法律的边缘
We all know we get close to the line sometimes.
但现在  我们都试着坚守在法律正义的一方
Now, we try to stay on the right side of the law.
你是想要成为一名好律师
You want to be a good lawyer,
但水至清则无鱼  你也知道你不得不这样做
you need to get close to that line and you know that.
这跟成为一名好律师无关
This wasn't about being a good lawyer.
这就是为了得到一份新工作
This was about getting a new job.
你才不是为了新工作
Not for you,
林德尔家的孩子才是  戴安
for the Rindell kid, Diane.
别再自责了
Stop kicking yourself.
我们正在对付的是
We are dealing with people who are coming at us
紧咬着我们最小的犯规之处不放的人
for the smallest infraction.
那么  我们该怎么为自己辩护
So, how do we defend ourselves?
夸大其词
Mere puffery.
你认真的
Seriously?
自从毕业我就没用过了  不过
I haven't used it since law school, but, hey.
我想我还从来没用过这招
I, I don't think I've ever used it.
-夸大其词
- Mere puffery.
这招真的有用吗
Does that even work?
我们试试就知道有没有用了
Uh, we will find out if it works.
我猜他们下一个会传召你
My guess is they call you next.
该死
Damn it!
老天  谁把你惹毛了
Yikes, who pissed you off?
我们能下次再找时间闲聊吗
Can we do the cute talk another time please?
也许我能帮你呢  什么事
Maybe I can help. What's up?
一串九位数  部分数字有重复
A nine-digit number, some repeats,
都和一些顶尖的首席执行官有关
all connected to top CEOs.
但它们都和纳税申报单号  法律案件号
But none of them are from tax returns
或员工编号无关
or legal cases or employee numbers.
你有试过社会保障号码吗
Did you try Social Security numbers?
当然
Yes.
也许这些是密码
Maybe they're passwords.
然后恰好都是九位数的密码
That just happened to all be nine digits?
也许这些和有钱混蛋的秘密帮会有关
Maybe they're part of some secret society of rich assholes.
怎么了
What?
我先澄清一下  我从来没赢过任何东西
Just so I'm clear, I never win at anything.
比方说买彩票  我选的号一个都没中过
If it's a lottery ticket, none of my numbers ever match up.
好吧
Okay.
我见过这个数字
I know this number.
这也是  还有这里
Here, too, and here.
这是我去年的全年薪资和纳税表
This is my W-2 from last year.
然后
And, uh,
这里  那个数字  那是什么
here. There, that number, what is that?
美国公司联邦税号
Federal Tax I.D. Number.
和这个一样
It's the same.
《雨人》  达斯汀·霍夫曼主演的电影
其饰演的角色"雨人"患有自闭症但对数字有超强记忆力
你是什么人啊  雨人
Who are you, Rain Man?
你还没见过我玩21点的风采呢
You should see me at the blackjack tables.
这份全年薪资和纳税表从哪来的
Who's this W-2 from?
我上一份工作  洛哈特&德克尔
My last job, Lockhart, Deckler...
靠
Oh, shit.
跟戴安有关系
It's about Diane.
杰·迪佩西亚
我并没有向博斯曼先生泄露
I did not slip Mr. Boseman any information
任何有关托比·肯德尔案子的信息
about the Toby Kendall case.
你确定吗
You're sure?
我确定
I am sure.
那就是博斯曼先生对诉讼投资人撒谎了
So Mr. Boseman lied to these litigation financiers.
不是  我猜他只是夸大其词了
No. My guess, it was mere puffery.
是吗
Really?
夸大其词是通过夸张
Mere puffery is the legally acceptable practice
进而达到推销作用的合法手段
of promoting through exaggeration.
没错  我知道是什么意思  谢谢
Yeah, I know what it is, thank you.
我们再来看看你为  最近被爆出庞氏骗局的
Let's turn to the work that you did for the Rindell Fund,
林德尔基金所做的工作吧
the recently exposed Ponzi scheme.
这是什么  洛哈特女士
What is this, Ms. Lockhart?
我不知道
I have no idea.
这不是一份林德尔基金的贵宾名单吗
Isn't it a list of VIP clients at the Rindell Fund?
可能是吧
It might be.
我也不清楚
I have no idea.
这些客户不就是林德尔基金
Aren't these the Rindell clients
铤而走险的原因所在吗
the Fund went the extra mile for?
倒填收益日期来避免交税
Backdating gains to avoid taxes?
再说一遍  我对此并不知情
Again, this is news to me.
是的  但是
Yes, but...
这难道不是你公司的税号吗
isn't that your firm's I.D. Number?
这里  这里  还有这里
There and there and there?
这难道这不是基金为你的法律服务买单的原因吗
Isn't that how the Fund billed your legal work?
再说一遍  这是我第一次看到
Again, this is my first time seeing...
还有这难道不是你安排林德尔的女儿
And isn't this why you arranged for the Rindell daughter
在你的新律所工作的原因吗
to get a job at your new work,
这样他们就不会揭发你的罪责了
so they wouldn't expose your culpability?
不是
No.
好吧  还好我们明天会请
Well, it's a good thing we have Henry Rindell
亨利·林德尔来出庭
coming in tomorrow to...
把这件事情说清楚
clear this matter up.
我必须辞职离开律所
I need to resign from this firm.
什么
Oh, yeah?
为什么
Why is that?
因为我马上就要被起诉了
Because I'm about to be indicted.
你  犯了什么罪吗
Are you... guilty of anything?
除了和小人做朋友以外
Other than being friends with the wrong people?
没有
No.
那么  你觉得我会因为律所的人
Then, do you think it surprises me
被盯上而感到意外吗
that someone inside this firm is being targeted?
亨利·林德尔已经听他调遣了
He has Henry Rindell in his pocket.
他准备要针对我来进行控告
He is going to get an indictment against me.
-假设他会  -我来这没多久  阿德里安
- Assume he does. - I haven't been here that long, Adrian...
那又有什么关系  戴安
What does that matter, Diane?
我才不会在他那样的混蛋面前害怕而逃跑
I'm not running scared from motherfuckers like him.
我要反击
I got to fight him.
你也要反击
You got to fight him.
所以  我们应该一起反击
So, we might as well fight him together.
真没想到会走到这一步
Bizarre that it's come to this.
是啊
Yeah.
可以这么说
That's one word.
你需要什么  宝贝
So what do you need, babe?
你明天会去向大陪审团作证是吗
You're testifying to the grand jury tomorrow?
-没错  -好吧
- Yeah. - Yeah.
你要作对戴安不利的证明
You're testifying against Diane?
不  我只是要说出事实
No, I'm telling the truth.
你所挑选的事实
Your alternative truth?
是的  戴安为基金提供了很多法律服务
Yeah, Diane did a lot of legal work for the Fund.
因为她是你的朋友
Because she was your friend.
不  是因为我们花钱雇了她
No, because we paid her.
这就是你让我从贾克斯叔叔电脑里
Is that why you had me get the Schtup list
拿鬼混名单的原因吗
from Uncle Jax's computer?
这样你就能利用它对付戴安了
So that you could use it against Diane?
制造她收受贿赂的假象
Make it look like she took a bribe?
不  这样我就有了筹码
No, so I would have some leverage.
你为了减刑就背叛了她
You betrayed her for a lighter sentence?
去坐牢的不是你  也不是你妈妈
You won't see any jail time, Mom won't either.
那你呢
And you?
我不想死在监狱里  玛娅
I don't want to die in prison, Maia.
我希望能有机会看到你生孩子
I want a chance to see you have kids.
我想抱抱我的外孙
I want to hold my grandkids.
协商结果是什么
What was the deal?
十年
Ten years.
不要说对戴安不利的证词
Don't testify against Diane.
什么  我不得不
What? I have to.
不  爸爸  如果他们提议减到十年监禁
No. Dad, if they're offering ten years,
那他们的胜面肯定很小
they must have a weak case.
这样做也是为了你
It's for you, too.
你要是这么做  爸爸
You do this, Dad,
如果我以后有了孩子
and if I ever have any kids,
你永远不会见到他们的
you'll never see them.
我永远不会让你见到他们
I'll never let you see them.
我爱你
I love you.
全体起立
All rise.
我们把本案审结吧
Okay, let's wind this down.
今天有什么情况
What do we have today?
我还有一个证人  法官阁下
I just have one more witness, Your Honor.
-你保证吗
- Promise?
是的  您不觉得有趣吗
I think so. Aren't you having fun?
我方反对这位证人出庭  法官阁下
We object to this witness, Your Honor.
又是你一个人  是吗  律师
All alone again, are you, counselor?
是的  克里斯特瓦先生认为有这位证人在
Yes, Mr. Kresteva thought it best to stay away
他不在场会比较好
given this next witness.
那我就很好奇了
Now I am curious.
你们知道这位证人是谁
You know who this witness is?
是的  传票今早才送到
Yes, the subpoena was served this morning.
我想重申我对允许此人
And I would like to reiterate my objection
出庭作证的反对意见
to permitting this man to testify.
奎因女士  为了她所谓的无辜
Ms. Quinn, for all her purported innocence,
似乎在不顾一切地贬损司法系统
seems hell-bent on compromising the integrity
法官阁下  我没有做过任何
Your Honor, I have done nothing
-的正直性  -这样的事
- of the judicial system. - of the sort.
天呐  你们这些人这么喜欢听自己说话吗
My God, you people love to hear yourselves talk.
传唤你的证人吧
Call your witness.
我们传唤亨利·林德尔
We call Henry Rindell.
-谢谢  -你还好吗
- Thank you. - Are you all right?
不太好
No, not really.
我很想能说事情会变好
I wish I could tell you it'll get easier.
我也希望您能如此对我说
I wish you could tell me that, too.
我猜这个人之后将会在
I imagine this is someone who's going to be testifying
大陪审团面前作证
in front of the grand jury later?
是的  法官阁下
It is, Your Honor.
而且我猜你们会承诺不向他问
And I imagine you're going to promise not to ask questions
有关他会如何作证的问题
about what he'll testify to?
不止如此  法官阁下
I'll go even further, Your Honor.
我对证人只有一个问题
I have just one question for this witness.
要反对吗  律师
Any objections, counselor?
那要看是什么问题了  法官阁下
Well, that depends on the question, Your Honor.
真是令人紧张的时刻
Quite the suspenseful moment.
请继续
Please, proceed.
林德尔先生
Mr. Rindell...
早上好
Good morning.
迈克·克里斯特瓦向你提供了什么交换条件
What did Michael Kresteva offer you in exchange
让你去大陪审团作证
for your grand jury testimony?
你看他干什么
What are you looking at him for?
我对这个问题不确定
I wasn't sure of the question.
那就看着我
Well, then, look at me.
迈克·克里斯特瓦向你提供了什么交换条件
What did Michael Kresteva offer you in exchange
让你去大陪审团作证
for your grand jury testimony?
他说他会向法官建议判我十年监禁
He said he would recommend to the judge
而非无假释的终身监禁
a sentence of ten years instead of life without parole.
没有其他问题了
No further questions.
助理总检察长威尔伯·丁肯
我对认罪协议毫不知情
I had no idea of the plea deal.
不  我没有批准
No, I did not authorize it.
是  参议员  我知道您的财产受损
Yes, Senator, I understand you lost money.
我把「太阳时报」接到一号线了
I've got the Sun-Times on line one.
告诉他们无可奉告
Tell them no comment.
迈克·克里斯特瓦来了
And Mike Kresteva's here.
让他进来  让我的电话都等等
Have him come in and hold my calls.
好的  不要
Yes. No.
原来那开关是这么用的
So that's what that does.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
恭喜什么
What for?
我刚刚被解职了
I was just relieved of my duties.
真的吗
You're kidding.
我是说  我很遗憾
I mean, I'm sorry.
给你  给你的小礼物
Here you go. Little present for you.
我什么没给你准备
Oh, and I didn't get you anything.
是的  那就这样吧
Yes, and let's keep it that way.
我很高兴这事结束了
Well, I'm just happy it's over.
有意思
That's funny.
什么有意思
What is?
我只是觉得好笑  你觉得这事结束了
Oh, I just think it's funny that you think this is over.
你继续
Here you go.
艾达
Ada.
我应该对你说谢谢
I owe you a thank you.
-你不必  -不  我要道谢
- No, you don't. - I do.
你本可以保护你自己
You could have protected yourself...
真的不用客气
Please, don't mention it.
但你保护了我
And instead, you protected me.
你给了我这份工作
You got me this job.
这是你应得的
You deserved it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们喝一杯吧
Let's get a drink.
不了  我
No. No, I...
我还是回家了
I better get home and...
好吧
Sure. Yeah.
我们喝一杯吧
Let's get a drink.